[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The water cycle is one of the natural processes that are ____ to most students.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The latest trend ____ the girls in the school is to wear different colour socks.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A rich parent has made a large ____ so that the school can buy new computers.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Try to ____ that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an instant solution.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Soviet workers have suffered a terrible ____ of a world-historical significance.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was a ____ move, but frankly we didn't have a choice.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Two grade B's and three grade A's ____ an excellent set of scores for the trimester.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most language lessons ____ the chance for the students to practise speaking.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not our ____ to send guests away without offering them something to eat.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My biggest regret about the book is that Gruchy did not ____ his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood ____ is to reduce the volume of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The following publications are available for ____ from the Florida Solar Energy Center.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Badly- behaved students often ____ the learning of other students in the class.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Knowing when to seek ____ for mental health disorders is important for parents and families.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government can ____ its message about the dangers of drinking if it increases the price of alcohol.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ made no comment on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you talk through a cloth it will ____ the sound of your voice.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government can advise people to save money for old age, but it cannot ____ them to do it.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He did not get a positive ____ to his request for a day's absence from work.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has only a ____ knowledge of English grammar - not enough to be an ESL teacher.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will encounter many difficulties but if you ____ in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is principally because they ____ the church and family as sources of emotional support.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most ____ architect to design a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher did not ____ that one of the students had been crying for most of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students will learn to appreciate what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an ____ are associated.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He continues to ____ all our efforts to help him.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The correct interpretation of this text requires recovering ____ implicit information that relies on commonsense knowledge.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to enlarge the ____ of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I usually keep a supply of ____ pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of ____ to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Increased ____ caused consumers to spend more and firms to invest more.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers fear that the problems in the Middle East may strain the ____ between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most programs have experienced the need to develop mechanisms to ____ involvement of parents and/or guardians in the juvenile drug court process.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If they want to ____ more business, they will have to reduce their prices.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student could not identify the ____ factors in a solution to the problem.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We faced an ____ problem over 10 years ago and couldn't solve it then, either.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do NOT wait until the last minute to try to ____ the exercise. If you wait until the day it is due, there is a good chance you will not finish on time.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this ____ will require the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After an ____ period of introduction and practice, the German course begins with Chapter 1 in the text Deutsch: Na klar!", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful ____ for both practical and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "That's probably the most fatuous ____ I've read on this website.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can't always ____ what happens to you, but you can always ____ how you react to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The additional time is ____ to enable him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) tend to be too ____ for many children.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to include more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few ____ facts.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "California's medical schools and major teaching hospitals are directly and ____ responsible for more than 200000 full-time jobs.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the ____ that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to publish if the ____ of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a official ____ of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your ____ grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will definitely fail this course.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When societies collapse into violence the ____ is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States ____ the natural ability to regulate food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The unpleasant incident in the computer lab is sure to ____ my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teachers allege that the school administration is secretly planning to ____ working hours.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While a considerable ____ of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was inevitable that the business would fail. It was badly run, and the products it sold were overpriced and of ____ quality.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is the ____ of educators to prepare themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Al Gore ____ did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his own carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was ____ luck that he got a good grade in the test. He hadn't studied for it at all.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The minister was unwilling to ____ on the changes in the price of oil in the next few months.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ the reasons for your lack of success.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "\"In the modern business world, the most important aspect of leadership is the ability to ____ an", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you move to London you will have to learn to ____ noise, crime and high prices.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Two grade B's and three grade A's ____ an excellent set of scores for the trimester.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a ____ of consistency in programs at conferences to develop the adviser's professional skills.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government will ____ in the coming election how unpopular its politics have been.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and ____ ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the transition from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 issue of Nature, the investigators report that female mice ____ the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thus, there is no question but that the donor intends this gift to be for the ____ use of Princeton University.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A regular driving license does not ____ the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the ____ of the situation even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This makes Kraay's work an unreliable ____ to whether globalisation really is making people in those countries better off.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early ____ start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or extend the building's ____ infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This has been the ____ of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to ____ the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A primary function of the system is to ____ the sharing of information with others.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to ____ with the settlers, Smith used force to acquire food.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She recognized the importance of introducing a plan that was ____ enough to meet the changing demands of the university.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to express by these two pieces, nor did I see any ____ in the work.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "With an ____ in the price of food and necessaries, the natural price of labor will rise; with the fall in their price, the natural price of labor will fall.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not ____ these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art form in Washington.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some tests may be very ____ but too costly to run, while others are less costly but not as precise.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We will deviate from this ____ throughout the semester, but the hand-out gives a good impression of our general focus.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the ____ before you criticize the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ is planning to extend the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe ____ did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to analyze its ____ methods.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The pattern of weight change through pregnancy was ____ across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We must trust the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a cause of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can ____ the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A small apartment in the middle of a busy city is not a ____ place to keep a large dog.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the ____ that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A foreigner who wants to become a ____ of the USA cannot have a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to ____ with it.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd create a zero point test with questions from the year before in ____ order with ____ answers.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He alleged that the ____ had adopted the policy of attacking the entire independent media rather than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in ____ and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the applicant waits until the time of decision to complete this form, it can cause a ____ delay in obtaining the visa document.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Congress seems to have taken a ____ approach to regulating a technology that is reinventing the very manner in which ideas are expressed.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The cost of establishing links will ____ as improvements are made to the underlying communication infrastructure.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The satellite photographs seem to ____ that North Korea is moving much of its army to the border with China.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A records check was unable to verify his claim that he possessed a ____ license.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The American public seems prepared to ____ some privacy for security.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people allege that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain ____ of its oil.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking ____ within the sentence, for instance before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final opportunity to ____ with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teaching is the ____ of the people who work at FIS.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Very few students are allowed to ____ the course, and permission is by petition only.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to ____ in the concept and institution of marriage.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At our 10th ____ symposium in late 2005, we posed this set of questions about Space Exploration: Who, What, When, Where, Why?", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is important that the government does not ____ significantly from what it promised during the elections.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In closing, I want to assert that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the ____ and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is possible to find the volume of an ____ by measuring the amount of water that it displaces.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research has demonstrated that good-looking people are more ____ to obtain a job than less good-looking people with the same qualifications.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Committee determines, in its ____ discretion, whether the College is entitled to claim ownership of the invention.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government minister expressed regret at her thoughtless ____ about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an ____ separate from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most significant risk ____ in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From then on, the government tried to ____ the communists of being enemies of the fatherland.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to ____ classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This validation will ____ him/her as a \"special student\" and will entitle him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people have complained about the ____ security procedures that have been introduced to UK airports.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most ____ decision of his career in order to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most schools do a lot to ____ their students of the dangers of smoking.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ your help, please. I can't do this on my own.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since exactly the same language can be used by those who disagree with him, the ____ is too general to be of any use.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing ____ when repeating the same strategy could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This ____ examines attitudes regarding the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government had to ____ that it had not succeeded in its plans to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research has demonstrated that good-looking people are more likely to ____ a job than less good-looking people with the same qualifications.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the room where we ____ the science equipment ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How could his final test scores ____ so strongly from the predictions we made?", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must ____ the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to exchange the book.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government should pay particular ____ to reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Since we can't observe it directly, we need to ____ it from the things we can observe.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it feasible to ____ someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The student will have an opportunity to be re-examined if the ____ attempt was not satisfactory.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of ____ grammar rules does always not correlate with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Car companies spend a ____ sum of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school has employed an ____ to advise on the best way to use computer technology in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Journalists were able to ____ the government's secret plan to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is fair to ____ the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment among older people.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She wanted to expand and to reorganize the departmental program but was not able to ____ the school administration.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not ____ that this is enough time for the entire project.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was ____ and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to collaborate and ____ their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and inform him that there is a ____ to his future children?", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You forgot just one ____ - your name at the top!", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to identify contexts where a traditional ____ might be required.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd create a zero point test with questions from the year before in ____ order with ____ answers.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company is selecting the best of ____ names that have been suggested for its new product.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Be sure to isolate and disinfect feeding ____ and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to offer more financial ____ to young married couples who want to buy a house.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few precise facts.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions ____ Iran over its nuclear program despite questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an ____ against bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government can ____ that people eat more healthily but it cannot force them to do so.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ area of Frankfurt is to the south east of the city center.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary ____ of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He states in his letter his strong opposition to a monarchy, which is not an ____ government for independence.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most basic ____ to develop is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government should do more to ____ immigrants who do not speak English.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "By the middle of May the ____ was critical and the rebellion seemed to get closer daily to the capital.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The business has decided to ____ a large reorganization in the attempt to increase profits.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school will ____ a new floor in the sport hall over the summer vacation.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The single, vital, ____ on which the true republic must found itself, he insists, is the ____ of good-will.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government reports a ____ decrease in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear ____ stations is among the most serious issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ showed much less growth than expected by the district's officials and residents.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new version of Microsoft's Internet Explorer lets you ____ pictures by using the mouse ball and the Control key.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a valid excuse, you can ____ the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Why do some children seem willing to ____ while others do not?", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The reporter is interested in the ____ of elementary school teachers who have at least 20 years of experience.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is ____ in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I thoroughly ____ this book to anybody interest in the vegetation of North America and to those studying similar vegetation in other parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All of those guidelines put together would make it nearly impossible to ____ a piece of art or literature.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and ____ treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of predominantly White jurors.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In order to ____ for the Olympic games 100-meter athletes need to have run under 10.2 seconds at least once this year.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences ____ which might contribute to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The substantial advantages of these close personal relationships far ____ the disadvantages of remaining small.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When dealing with a real, ____ system such as a robot, however, this approach is simply not practical.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is vital that we find better and cheaper ways to ____ energy than by burning coal or oil.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the completely rational ____ of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The expulsion of a student for smoking in the toilets caused a big ____ in the school.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a ____ of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can diminish the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no shame in ____ if you have tried your best.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When parents decide to send their children to a fee -paying school, ____ becomes a commodity.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Manufacturing companies are finding it difficult to make a profit, because of the ____ in the price of oil.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His ____ measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable statistic and you should simply ____ it.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The head of FEMA said that the victims of Hurricane Katrina who failed to evacuate bore some ____ for that failure.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Before this century there was little ____ between them; indeed, they did not think of themselves as two distinct kinds of people.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that random is ____ the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have ____ to your medical record, thus is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Did anyone ____ to solve question 11?", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For reasons that are not yet completely clear, practice and theory usually ____ at this point.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse ____ of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These two-word verbs ____ one other problem, besides not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors have not been able to establish the precise ____ of the patient's illness.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company directors are ____ that business will improve in the new year.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the question. I didn't understand what you said.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to conserve energy and help ____ to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a conflict from a ____ of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an ____ separate from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Both of these deep sky objects are reserved for telescopes, so be sure to ____ them from a dark site.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many students do poorly in tests because they ____ to answer the questions. It's as simple as that.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will culminate in a ____ of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The use of this seemingly simple system does not ____ an undeveloped technological ability on the part of 9th century Hindus.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student's answer may not ____ all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The prime ____ of a strong academic vocabulary is that it helps you to read school textbooks more efficiently.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She began to notice that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She claimed that the disproportionate number of non-native speakers in the survey did not ____ the results.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university must not neglect issues which affect staff and students, in ____ graduate students.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I was unable to ____ the reason for Angelica's sudden departure at the beginning of the second trimester.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ street demonstrations against its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The robot will ____ medications, and alert help if the patient falls.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Above all, a teacher must be ____ when dealing with requests for grade changes and other related matters.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most important ____ to her learning is that she never does her homework.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions ____ in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How the ____ changed when he entered a room: it was warm, electric, somehow bigger.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government failed to suppress street demonstrations ____ its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government intends to found a new organization to help young people find ____ jobs.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every necessary precaution has been taken to provide up-to-date, ____ information in this website.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I hesitate to put all of my ____ notes online because I do want students to attend the ____s.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I regard what people actually do in practice as far more significant and worthy of formalization than what ivory-tower logicians ____ in principle.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their ____ responsibility to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the essay is good, but the rest is of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable ____ and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On the rare occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than ____ hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Court determined, however, that evidence concerning Ms. Lewinsky was not ____ to the core issues in this case.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please ____ your answer to a maximum of 100 words.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ for her frequent absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The School of Medicine provides a Web server for Medical Center organizations and departments to ____ institutional information.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Odland demonstrated the ability to run a significant ____ with a wide geographical spread.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student council can ____ suggestions, but it has no power to make changes happen.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most companies guarantee to ____ machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I would also ____ that you contact your physician for further information.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many students ____ their chances of examination success because they only start to work hard a few weeks before.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the essay is good, but the rest is of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My parents ____ a lot of money from their investments in internet companies.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sometimes it is ____ to exert force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important to note that the ____ at which refracted light travels is dependent upon the density of the materials it is traveling through.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the region is sure to ____ an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first ____ those principles and then consider the subsequent problems.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a complex problem, and its solutions will ____ new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government can advise people to save money for old age, but it cannot ____ them to do it.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Despite looking for Osama Bin Laden for many years, the USA still do not know his ____ location.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to ____ its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a voluntary tax sheltered annuity program should ____ their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In most countries of the world you need to get a ____ before you can drive a car.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's not ____ to do all the questions on the sheet.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to persuade patients to stop smoking. The ____ is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Repeat this ____ until only a small amount of pressure is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would ____ the quality of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Plants that possess certain traits or characteristics not ____ to the entire species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In our society, which is far from ____ in its beliefs and values, reaching consensus on any issue is significantly difficult.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the ____ of poverty and poor school performance.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A very ____ response in real time is needed to record the optical emission while the gamma-ray burst is in progress.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The detective was able to ____ from the size of the footprints that the thief was probably a woman or child.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to ____ their services.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ minister has decided to cancel the planned visit to Batavia in view of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "European governments strongly condemn the kidnapping of a German ____ worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The director had to ____ the school play when 4 of the cast fell ill the day before the first performance.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written ____ within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The results indicated that there was a significant improvement in fluency, a ____ improvement in accuracy, but no improvement in complexity.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My ____ tells me that there is more to her learning problems than the parents are willing to say.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A layer of this cement three tenthousandths of an inch thick over one square inch will ____ a weight of 7000 pounds.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ should consider reducing its prices, otherwise people will just not buy there.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Tobacco smoke was a ____ of life up through the 1970s.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What is the exact change in ____ of the water when it freezes as ice?", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction ____ junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase income tax after ____ demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In my ____ the government's argument for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be ____ and to highlight all that is important.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you submit your application in person, there will be a ____ of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These ____ and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many economists associate the ____ in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Based on his research, Healey developed a system that combined the display of multiple values into a single ____ element.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter ____ to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I'm trying to ____ a machine that will do my homework for me. - Good luck!", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The result will be an ____ and substantial increase in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your English is gradually improving, but you'll have to make greater ____ if you want to get better more quickly.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My teacher has the ____ of telling us the homework in the last minute of the lesson. It's not good.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The robot will ____ medications, and alert help if the patient falls.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is principally because they ____ the church and family as sources of emotional support.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students will undertake comprehensive analysis of several works and will ____ a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady ____ in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our focus is to ____ each student to achieve their full potential as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is beyond the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the ____ will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise ____ of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But it is not a substitute for ____ food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Large numbers of older adult students do not possess the basic computer knowledge required to ____ a job.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should demonstrate a significant ____ of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to classify the world's languages into one ____ genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally ____ a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Why do anthropologists ____ the word 'primitive'?", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost ____ over the conduct of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would ____ to refute or ignore these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company's ____ plan was to close down only one of their factories. Because of continuing bad sales, however, they were forced to close three of them.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A company's success or continuation should not depend on the service of outside ____ contractors.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English version must ____ the submission.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ structure of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Probably every introductory science text in the world includes a first chapter ____ on the scientific method.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ people without jobs to business that are looking for workers.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Groups should ____ the instructor if a member is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is easy to use the internet to gather a lot of information. Whether it is of good ____ is a different matter!", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary ____ of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not the government's role to ____ what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people say that drugs like cannabis should be made legal to allow the government to ____ its sale.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The easiest way to ____ documents in .pdf is by using the Adobe Acrobat software.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's a ____ attack on any community's authority to develop and implement housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must verify that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to ____ you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This interesting ____ offers the student of neuroscience access to an immense amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They have made a ____ error in the way they are thinking about the opportunities and problems their business face.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The US Senate voted yesterday to provide \ufffd\ufffd4 billion for antiviral drugs and other measures to ____ for a feared influenza epidemic.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to reveal the secret until means have been ____ to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging task for the employers to determine the factors that ____ job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The student who had forgotten his homework was fortunate that the teacher was ____ that day.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not survive without support.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is virtually dead.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The professor was not certain that the work contained the student's ____ ideas.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "17% reported that their ____ was not at all adequate.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advances in technology have increased the ____ of life and the ____ of change.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has decided to block financial ____ to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to ____ the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Iraq is ____ in a state of civil war.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has set a clear limit on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the ____ every year.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This section of the GED web ____ provides several example questions from each part of the GED Tests.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Not everyone agrees with the government's ____ of putting illegal immigrants into prison.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was a chance to try out something different and immerse myself completely in another culture and it was a ____ I did not regret.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The owner of the organization has the ____ to make decisions.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My hypothesis is that parents are not happy with the ____ their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to define any of these ____ terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a resident of Indiana since at least December 31 of the ____ year.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Someone forgot to ____ the book with the result that it contains serious errors of grammar or punctuation.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is a controversial ____ that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some people the ____ of a car is more important than its price or performance.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Choose active, ____ verbs to invigorate your scientific or engineering professional papers, thesis, and reports.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hydrogen has the potential to ____ a clean, storable, transportable and renewable source of energy that can meet the need for power throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is still somewhat of a risk to ____ things on the internet.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You must write a ____ of 3 pages for your final report.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Another significant ____ was provided by the results of the post-hoc test of Recognition Motivation.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As yet there has been no ____ example of the sighting of a spacecraft from another world.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student who had forgotten his homework was fortunate that the teacher was ____ that day.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ of this cement three tenthousandths of an inch thick over one square inch will support a weight of 7000 pounds.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to ____ him and inform him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While the system has offered men the opportunity to become owners of small factories, this opportunity rests on the unpaid ____ of female family members.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a ____ idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are focused on creating the technology and applications that will ____ daily media consumers to become daily media producers.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ kind of language problem is to fill in the gap in a sentence with a missing word.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no ____ of him passing the course. He has been away too many times this year.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thanks to his ____ in the last Grand Prix of the season, Michael Schumacher won the World Championship.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have not got these words in the right order. In German the main verb must be the second ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The State Department has seen a ____ increase in passport applications being filed since a recent change in policy.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Too much stress can ____ problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is to the government's credit that they refused to ____ in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The supervisor perceived Pullard as an incompetent employee, but did not ____ that he might be a security problem.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The festival was a ____ disaster: there was no food, no medical assistance, the rain and overpopulation made the place a living hell.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The problem for France was that the population did not ____ of responsible citizens which were necessary for the desired liberal system.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the number of sections to be taught does not correspond to the number of students, you need to ____ the reason.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The name of this website is 'A ____ to learning English.'", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This survey is being used to ____ information about the current level of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was not willing to retreat from previous ____ commitments.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is slightly down from the 19 percent failure ____ last year but still significantly above the failure ____ in other freshmen subjects.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They were small-minded people and could not ____ students who were superior them.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to live a long and healthy life, it is essential that you eat well and get ____ of exercise.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government refused to ____ from its plan to ban smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We wanted to ____ that the resonators worked, and our major theoretical assumptions were correct.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will never win the ____ against drug-taking.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Theatre is not the correct ____ for such a performance, since it is a matter of the virtual as well as the actual.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Hydrogen has the ____ to provide a clean, storable, transportable and renewable source of energy that can meet the need for power throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You would ____ improve your chances of success if you made more effort.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students must ____ a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical passage into English.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will watch a ____ of films about Ancient Rome. This first one is about Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Computer viruses ____ themselves to documents such as word processing files and spreadsheets.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Committee determines, in its ____ discretion, whether the College is entitled to claim ownership of the invention.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Maharaj says that he did not particularly care for the Broadway production of Side Show because he felt it failed to ____ the writers' true intentions.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The referee of a football match can ____ the offside flag of his or her linesman.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists devise a new way to ____ gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students needed to devote ____ time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to improve the performance of these devices, but ____ there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even though the South voted solidly against Lincoln, they could not ____ his victory.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police did not have the necessary ____ to cut the man free from the crashed car.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "FLO plays the key role as an ____ for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs ____ walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs instead of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ____ attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Employees must have worked for the State for at least five years, and have a ____ record of sick leave usage and work performance.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To ____ the highest positions in American politics it is necessary to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is set to suffer a heavy ____ in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Because of the ____ of wheat, due to persistent wet weather, the price of bread has risen in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Injuries ____ when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the interior of the brain.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She wanted to expand and to reorganize the departmental program but was not able to ____ the school administration.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Austen does not convince us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and ____ in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Next the teacher must ____ that nicotine in tobacco products is addictive.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Health Minister has made the ____ request that parents make sure their children eat enough fruit and vegetables.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Delivery of safe and timely care is a huge ____ given the complexities of modern medicine.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors were unable to ____ the man who was pulled out of the icy river.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't appreciate a ____ from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a ____ introduction to some of the main ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This validation will identify him/her as a \"special student\" and will ____ him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the standard ____ for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most powerful typhoon in over a ____ should break south of Shanghai early on Wednesday.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your answers exhibit a ____ of care and effort.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Every necessary ____ has been taken to provide up-to-date, accurate information in this website.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A small apartment in the middle of a busy city is not a ____ place to keep a large dog.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should demonstrate a significant ____ of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was in 1827, near the beginning of his time ____ from the Allan family, that Poe witnessed his first collection of poetry.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nature was an ____ part of ancient Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I need to ____ the importance of meeting the project deadlines.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his ____ to correctly inform the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To attain the highest positions in American politics it is ____ to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our aim was to determine whether the association between HPV infection and cervical cancer is ____ worldwide.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Historically, there was compensation for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and ____ of funds for compensation programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ASVAB is a mental ____ test given to all potential entrants to the Armed Services.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an episode of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common ____ than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, ____ underlying issues, and suggest alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The recent conference about green energy failed to ____ the interest of the British public.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to settle the dispute by the efforts of the ____ community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will need to request a ____ leave of absence with USC if you intend to be away from more than 3 days.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I hope to ____ a good grade in my grammar test.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You must enter the US using the visa document issued by the ____ you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to persuade patients to stop smoking. The ____ is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was ____ that the business would fail. It was badly run, and the products it sold were overpriced and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its ____ colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a ____ of student work in the corridor outside of the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Scientists are working on a robot that can ____ to the deepest parts of the Pacific Ocean.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to compile a full application including: ____ sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to fail to prepare properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company's ____ is that they will increase exports by 20% next year.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's a serious attack on any community's ____ to develop and implement housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all available sick leave for that ____ reporting period.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they ____ did not conform to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people employ an ____ when they want to buy or sell a house.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ASVAB is a mental ____ test given to all potential entrants to the Armed Services.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This international ____ course has been especially created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most important ____ of living near the school is that I can go home for lunch every day.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The syllabus must clarify how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's ____ grade.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on ____ and condition.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a ____ of student work in the corridor outside of the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to examine further ways to continue this great benefit to the company's ____ as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration ____ to modify its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to ____ the unacceptable risk that the present system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ reasons for his academic success. The most important one is his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the ____ was not able to eliminate discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an ____ to organize your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He said several times that money was not a ____ in the decision, and it was not about safety alone.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter prior to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a ____ response.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "David Malik maintains that most students are not able to ____ teaching effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations ____ new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices ____ decreased until virtually zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Seed cleaning is not an ____ that requires a large amount of labor.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "About a quarter of the elementary and secondary students typically did not ____ with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Food irradiation can be an important tool in the war ____ illness and death from foodborne diseases.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must ____ achievement that is over and above regular course activities.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But he did not ____ himself to theoretical matters alone. He now drew attention to the lack of American minority students on campus.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At a certain point in your journey, you might discover that the ____ you chose is just too vast.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not get a prompt ____ to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to transform it into a research project is not ____ to succeed.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My ____ opinion of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Yet there were conflicts there too, and the immigrants did not ____ easily and completely into Israeli culture.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government reduced its ____ to the Arts Council after it was found that much of the money had been wasted.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most doctors consider ____ a superior way to lose weight than going on a diet.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The format for references must ____ to the guidelines in the approved style manual.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unit did not ____ nuclear weapons in as much detail as some of my students would have liked.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To ____ the project, a special event will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My ____ is that she has started working too late to pass her examinations.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is the ____ choice for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material environment of Louisiana, it did not ____ the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not apply to Cheney's ____ force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Preparing yourself for a ____ in oceanography is probably one of the most interesting and rewarding (yet difficult) paths to travel.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you can ____ the problems you had with your last history project, I will be able to help you better with your current one.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of regular water quality data collection to statistically ____ a trend.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not ____ a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Health Department is advertising on TV to ____ the message about the importance of healthy eating and exercise.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In most modern car factories robots ____ the larger parts.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a thorough analysis, ____ it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While addiction and drugs are serious problems in society that ____ a humane approach, there is no room for nonsense if we want to achieve success.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking ____ actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of business between Europe and Asia has greatly increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Generic skills cannot be considered as ____ of subject matter. Moreover, a good part of teaching involves thinking, problem- solving, and decision making.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An important ____ of the course is the unit on grammar.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation ____ that is used in virtually all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On the one ____ I got to school early, the building was closed because of a fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and ____ treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of predominantly White jurors.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Choose active, ____ verbs to invigorate your scientific or engineering professional papers, thesis, and reports.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My hypothesis is that parents are not happy with the ____ their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This ____ is not rare: 99 percent of patients experience a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In most countries of the world ____ is compulsory for all children.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Transportation is not an important ____ in the marketing cost of the new product.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of your ideas and organization is much more important than the quantity of words you write.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study ____ in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In this problem you have to ____ that x=7.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the ____ that urban life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Use ____ words and phrases; don't drain the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot ____ the war of aggression against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school had ____ exam results to last year, with the exception except that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The typewriter is more or less ____ now that we have computers and keyboards.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to compile a full application including: ____ sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Conversely, rising wage rates often ____ workers to try to work fewer hours as they become rich enough to afford more leisure.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Vegetable crops are the most important ____ group for small farms in southern states and their importance is expected to increase.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Advances in technology have increased the ____ of life and the ____ of change.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the battle ____ global warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to improve in English, I ____ that you read plenty of books for pleasure.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good ____ reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ensure that the way we talk must not ____ any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for adequate ____ and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We did not base our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or ____ of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She found that the document had no ____ and conflicted with the assessments of military intelligence.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy demand to ____ costs.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A sound card is an ____ component of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "No individual can have much ____ on the environment, but people working together can make a big difference.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An important ____ of the course is the unit on grammar.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The director had to ____ the school play when 4 of the cast fell ill the day before the first performance.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I have no ____ of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to earn more money!", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will need to provide a ____ of recent writing so that your English level can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the ____ to talk about his own school days.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Fully 10 percent of the U.S. population has some form of learning disability; the true ____ may in fact be higher.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His research helped establish that ____ DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the ____ that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This tells us that there is a very large market for us to expand into, if we take ____ of the opportunities as they arise.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Law School will not ____ you to take a course pass/fail unless you have received written permission.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It took the Brazilian football player a little while to adjust to the ____ and hardness of the English football league.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Desdemona is passive for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the ____ for her death.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students must demonstrate ____ of a competent reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Scientists are hoping that it may soon be possible to ____ the weather.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a ____ to investigate the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an ____ against bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and ____ financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to ____ the impact of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a ____ interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In fact, most nations do not ____ immigrants for permanent settlement.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unless we reverse the trend, the ____ will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of staff scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you submit your application in person, there will be a ____ of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not acknowledge the ____ developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of your writing is not at all clear to me.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People are more ____ to migrate in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Where did you ____ your knowledge of ocean ecology?.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school had to pay a small ____ to the parents of the boy who hurt his arm on the ski trip.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Using a computer program makes it easier to ____ long pieces of writing.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food ____ could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Computer hard disk cleaning is not an ____ that many people perform very frequently.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Are you ____ of the fact that you may fail the course?", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to ____ his concept against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every necessary ____ has been taken to provide up-to-date, accurate information in this website.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and ____ related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lack of financial aid is a significant ____ on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government's new proposals are too vague. They need to be ____ about what they expect people to do.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is clear that the Mid-Zambezi Project has failed in its ____ of controlling immigration.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But he did not confine himself to theoretical matters alone. He now drew attention to the ____ of American minority students on campus.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Summarizing or paraphrasing is expressing the original idea or information in your ____ words.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or ____ the building's unique infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All of those guidelines put together would make it nearly impossible to ____ a piece of art or literature.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Desdemona is ____ for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the blame for her death.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The website shows how schools ____ and use their resources.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He may ____ to any political party he pleases, or he may ____ to none.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A great ____ of discussion focused on observations which could solve the mystery by testing the predictions of the various hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student was hardly active with the experiment and did not ____ to contribute.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's a total ____ that young girls are being pressured into near-starving themselves into being too thin.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The desire to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a ____ human drive.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions suppress the need for communication or being able to freely ____ your emotions?", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ is of a dimension that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government would like to reform the health service but the doctors are ____ their proposals.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She discussed the ____ for implementing the system through April 2003 and outlined several potential advantages of the system.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She chose to reject the hypothesis that there is an increased ____ of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His father's ideas were ____ and out of time. They were traditional views that were losing much of their appeal.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To ____ their high salary, top managers like to refer to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take regular exercise.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate attempt to ____ the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This survey examines attitudes ____ the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in English, I recommend that you read plenty of books for pleasure.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no point in getting angry with security staff at airports. They have no ____ but to follow orders.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His ____ measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power cycle failure, but this is not a ____ for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teacher did not completely ____ the students' suggestion, but she first needed to discuss it with the principal.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you ____ will come from the M31 incident - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will ____ in a series of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They did not provoke an ____. They responded to an ____ from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you work harder, you will ____ a better grade next term.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If there is any question whether the individual might have a ____ problem, the mental health professional should recommend a complete examination.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a result of the massive amount of evidence for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely ____ that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main ____ of this ESL course is to improve students' ability in academic writing.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate attempt to ____ the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Actually if two ____ tones of the same frequency and intensity are produced simultaneously, they will combine.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ between the workers and the management improved when flexible working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are in ____ pain you should consult a doctor.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people say that drugs like cannabis should be made legal to allow the government to ____ its sale.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It would not be ____ to deviate from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government surely cannot fail to ____ that its attempts to reduce teenage pregnancy are not working.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor condition and are in ____ need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The rat lungworm, is the ____ cause of eosinophilic meningitis worldwide.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much ____ by conducting a retreat after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in order to ____ his political survival.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Check with your academic advisor if you are uncertain whether this will count as a ____ towards your graduation.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This process is more ____ in those sciences in which the technological requirements have increased to a significant extent.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers identified aspects intrinsic to the task of teaching, such as their interactions with students and their capacity to ____ student achievement.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to announce their ____ before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A large ____ of the country is under water after the heavy rainfall of the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "European countries have decided to collaborate in an ____ to reduce illegal immigration.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new ____ will affect all immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "ESS is for students who envision getting involved in the social ____ in any capacity: as volunteer consultants, board members, managers, or entrepreneurs.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to ____ the vast mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Corms have shapes similar to bulbs, but do not ____ fleshy scales.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you choose to do nothing to ____ to the changing conditions, you will probably make yourself miserable.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Using a new technique to trap and ____ single particles with lasers, an international group of researchers have demonstrated that Brownian motion of a single particle behaves differently than Einstein theorized one century ago.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your supervisor has been provided with the above information and should be able to ____ any questions you may have.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to measure such a huge ____ as the earth.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people believe that the government will not ____ with its plans to decriminalize cannabis.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will ____ students of their ability to think for themselves if you never set them challenging questions.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is the correct key ____ on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please ____ my possessions and not use them without asking permission.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to reflect on, critically analyze, and ____ their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of most big cities around the main train station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will not prevail unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to ____ in public service.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The information that you ____ in today's lesson will enable you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of ____ and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doing so will probably provoke a strong negative ____ from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This unnecessary war will ____ the government plans to reduce tax.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Bush's principal ____ for re-election is his war on terrorism, but in fact that's one of the principal reasons he should not be re-elected.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This ____ that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't ____ career counseling.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot ____ it.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must verify that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to ____ you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He did not ____ the problem until too late.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Caesar showed no reluctance to ____ the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He did not get a positive ____ to his request for a day's absence from work.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Here you can ____ areas for investment of resources to advance the University in its health sciences, education, research, service and outreach missions.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only ____ been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We know it's not 100% correct, but it's the best ____ that we can produce at this time.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not ____ that medical science will find a cure for cancer in the near future.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In a ____ between the school and the parents, it is usually the school that will prevail.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Significant progress has been toward reaching this goal through the ____ workforce planning effort as well as specific unit managerial decisions.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}]]